Woodrow Wilson Collection, 1837-1986 (bulk 1883-1924 ): Preliminary Finding Aid MC168
Public Policy Papers
- Series 10: Papers of Others About Woodrow Wilson, 1837-1986 October 14; 58 boxes; 2 folders
  - Family, 1837-1962; 4 boxes; 2 folders
    - Photographs, 1905-1917; 1 box
      - 2 photographs Hoyt, Mrs. Nathan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Photograph Wilson, Annie Josephine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Photograph (autograph) Wilson, Edith Bolling, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Photograph Wilson, Edith Bolling, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - 4 photographs Wilson, Edith Bolling, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Photograph Wilson, Edith Bolling, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - 4 photographs Wilson, Eleanor Randolph (Nell) Mrs. William G. McAdoo, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - 4 photographs, [1914], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Photograph Wilson, Ellen Axson, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - 12 photographs Wilson, Ellen Axson, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Print of portrait by Wilson, Frederic Yates, Jessie Woodrow (Mrs. Francis B. Sayre), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - 3 photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - Photograph Wilson, Joseph Ruggles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Photograph Wilson, Joseph Ruggles and Jessie Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - Photograph Wilson, Margaret and Wilson, Jessie, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - 2 photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - Photograph Wilson, Margaret Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - 4 photographs Wilson, Margaret Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 29)
      - Photographs of her recitals, European tours and David, Elizabeth H. and David, Ross, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - 2 photographs, Woodrow Harriet (Hattie) (Mrs. Edward Freeman Welles), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 31)
      - 2 photographs Woodrow, Helen Sill (2), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 32)
      - Photograph Woodrow, Thomas, Sr., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 33)
      - Photograph unidentified, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Material and Printed Matter, 1880-1914; 1 box; 2 folders
      - Autographs, Wilson, Jessie Woodrow, 1882; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 35)
      - Autographs, Wilson, Joseph Ruggles, Jr, 1882; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 35)
      - Autographs, Bones, Marion McG, 1880; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 35)
      - Calling cards, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 36)
      - Locks of hair (Wilson, Ellen Axson), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 37)
      - Locks of hair Axson, Margaret Randolph, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 38)
      - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 39)
      - Card Brown, Marjorie, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 39)
      - Envelope to Wilson, Joseph R. (Mrs.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 39)
      - A memorial tribute to Wilson, Ellen Axson by the United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1914; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 40)
      - Regarding Family of Axson, Margaret Jane Hoyt (Mrs. Edward Axson), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 41)
      - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 42)
      - Newspaper clippings, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 43)
      - Newspaper clippings, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 44)
      - Wilson, Edith Bolling – "As I Saw It" SEP tearsheets, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 45)
      - Wedding Book: Marriage of Wilson, Eleanor and McAdoo, William Gibbs, 1914 May 17; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder vOLUME 1)
  - Wilson, Margaret Woodrow (including David, Elizabeth Harbison and David, Ross), 1917-1936; 2 boxes
    - "A Rhyming Narrative of our E.E.Tour, 1918-1919" AmsS Wilson, Elizabeth H., David, Margaret Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Poem "We planned to start at 9 o'clock" AMs David, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - I Played Their Accompaniments TMS David, Elizabeth H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - I Played Their Accompaniments proofs, David, Elizabeth H., Wilson, Margaret Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Lyrics some written by David, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 2 ALsS to Elizabeth (by Wilson, Margaret W.) David, 1920; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 5 TLsS, 1918-1936; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 2 ALsS to David, Harmonie, [1915], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence to Wilson, Margaret W., 1 TLS, 1919; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence to Wilson, Margaret W., 1 ANS, 1918; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence to Wilson, Margaret W., Document, 1917; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence by David, Elizabeth to family from Europe, [1919], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence to David, Elizabeth and David, Ross including letters by Bones, Helen Woodrow, Johnson, Herschel V., Kesch, Father A., Pershing, John J., Madame Schvmann-Heink, Trask, Katrina, Wilson, Edith Bolling, Y.M.C.A., et al., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence to Atherton, Harmonie David Miscellaneous (Mrs. Carlyle A. Atherton) daughter of David, Elizabeth and David, Ross, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence Misc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Documents, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Calling cards, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Invitations to Wilson, Elizabeth, and David, Ross, cards of appreciation to David, Elizabeth and Ross, Woodrow, Margaret, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Itinerary of War Relief Tours (xerox copies included), 1917-1919; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Recital programs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Printed matter misc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper clippings (including David, Elizabeth H. and David, Ross), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper clippings (including David, Elizabeth H. and David, Ross), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Memorabilia, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Woodrow Wilson as Subject (Writings, such as Reminiscences, Theses, Dissertations, etc.), 1894-1973; 2 boxes
    - Extracts from diary copies. 2 pp Barringer, Brandon, 1913; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Bibliography of Wilson, Woodrow writings and addresses by Clemons, Harry; Clemons, George; Drown, Dobbin; Leach, Howard S. including correspondence to Leach, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Howard Seavoy Leach Correspondence about Woodrow Wilson Bibliographical Work, 1917-1924; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 2a)
      AR.2008.153
    - "Wilson's Attitude toward Dean West" TMs, with TLS to Miss Turnbull, Capps, Edward, Undated, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - "Some Personal Recollections of Woodrow Wilson" MsS 13pp (A chapter from Woodrow Wilson, Some Princeton Memories) Conklin, Edwin Grant, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - "A Brief Visit with President Wilson 3 pp Gipson, Lawrence Henry, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - "My acquaintance with Woodrow Wilson..." AMS 24 pp (a chapter from Woodrow Wilson, Some Princeton Memories, Myers, William Starr, including, AL (copy) by Wilson, Jessie to Harper, 1894 and ANS by Harper to Myers, William Starr, 1945, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Poem "The Face of Wilson" Hawes, Fred M. TMs (carbon), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Henneman, John, 'The Work of a Southern Scholar' 21 pages Wilson, Woodrow Biography, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 7a)
    - "For President: Woodrow Wilson" Typescript of an oration, 3 pp. Holland, Nicholas S, 1912; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Transcripts of 2 spirit messages to Ingle by Wilson, Woodrow, Ingle, Edith, 1971; 1973; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Address to the Board of Directors of the Missouri, Kansas, and Texas Railroad Company, TMs (carbon), with related correspondence "The Joline Letter" regarding Bryan, W. J.; Joline, Adrian H, 1907; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - "Woodrow Wilson a play in four acts," Kissel, Carter, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Notes from a diary written while in France with Woodrow Wilson, Transcript of Letter to "Dear Johnny" Lamb, Albert Richard, 1957; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - "Woodrow Wilson: His Education in World Affairs" AMs (carbon), 18pp Address delivered at the Harvard commemoration of the birth of Wilson, Woodrow Longer, William L, 1956; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Draft of a paper on the private life of President Wilson TMs, 9 pp., 1916; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Patten, Thomas Gedney to Tumulty, Joseph P., 3 pp., 1921 April 11; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 14b)
    - "Wilson Fight Against Secret Pacts Defense of the Yugoslav National Frontiers" (At the Peace Conference in Paris, 1919) TMsS, 25pp, including a TLS to "Princeton University", 1967; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - "Woodrow Wilson in 1900-1912" TMs (carbon) 11pp. TLS, to Savage, Henry L, 1953; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - "Professor Woodrow Wilson's Philosophy of Education" TMs (carbon), Osborn, George C., undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - "Address at the Presentation of a portrait-bust of president Woodrow Wilson in Nassau Hall, November 7, 1945" TMs, 5pp, incl. TLS, by Root to Savage, Henry L.; Root, Robert K, 1946; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Printed Matter Newspaper clipping from "Pitching Horseshoes" Also: TNS: (initialed) by Dodds, Harold W. to Boyd, Julian P.; Rose, Billy, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Address given at the dinner to governor-elect Edwards TMs (carbon), 17pp. Saunders, William Lawrence, 1919; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - "Statement... in regard to the cast of the right hand of President Wilson, Woodrow" TMsS (notorized) 2 pp. Spicer-Simsen, Theodore, 1928; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - TMs regarding Glee club, Steinwald, Osmar P., undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Review of Wilson Road to the White House by Link, Arthur S., TMs 29 pp. 2 TMsS (carbon) Tucker, William Le Grand, 1948 July 22; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - "What Woodrow Wilson Means to Japan" TMs 5 pp. Tsurumi, Yusuke, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - "Memorandum on Young Men's Talk" TMs (carbon) from the Princeton Alumni News, van Dyke, Tartius, 1943 January 15; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - "Three Interviews with Citizens of Princeton, N.J. Who Knew Woodrow Wilson." TMsS, 4 pp - Skillman, Charles, 1949 Durner, Will, 1949 Bradford, Edward W., 1956, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - BA Thesis "International Organization as Advocated and Advanced by Woodrow Wilson and Franklin Delano Roosevelt", 1945; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - MA Thesis "Apprenticeship for the Presidency: A Study of Woodrow Wilson as Governor of New Jersey" 2 copies Lewis, McMillan, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Doctoral Dissertation on Wilson, Woodrow, 1954-1957; 1 box
      - Correspondence, Shawi, Hishamal, 1954-1957; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Summary of thesis, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Table of Contents – Chapter IV pp. 1-145, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Chapter v – Chapter VIII pp. 146-285, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Chapter IX – Chapter XII pp. 287-425, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Chapter XIII – Bibliography pp. 426-556, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1887-1952; 4 boxes
    - Collections, 1887-1952; 3 boxes
      - Farrand, Wilson, 1887-1914; 1 box
        - Statement at Trustees Meeting 3 TMss (carbons) Farrand, Wilson, 1910 January 13; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 1)
        - 2 resolutions urging acceptance of the gift of Procter, William Cooper for the Princeton Graduate College, 1910; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 2)
        - I took my seat in the Princeton Board of Trustees... AMs with copies of 2 letters to Pyne, Moses Taylor, typescript, 1909; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 3)
        - In the spring of 1904... typescript with carbon, as well as a TLS by D'Olier, Franklin to Farrand, 1902; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - In his speech to Delaware Alumni Association... TMs (carbon), undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - I began teaching in 1887 at the Newark Academy... AMs, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - Coming out from luncheon at the Essex Club... AMs with typescript (anecdote of ex-senator Smith, James Jr.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - 2 parodies Ye Knighte of Ye Holi Kail, or Toe Proudde to Fygghte The Serpent in the Wilderness, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - Horoscope of Wilson, Woodrow, by Thompson, Catharine Howard, 1914; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence – Scudder, Edward W., Elder, William S., Fisher, Janon, Harper, George M'Lean, Wilson, Woodrow, 1909-1910; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - Printed Matter, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Lewis, McMillan, 1949-1952; 1 box
        - Woodrow Wilson of Princeton proofs. Lewis, McMillan, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - Review of Woodrow Wilson of Princeton ALS to Henry L. Savage, 1952; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 2)
        - List of correspondents ANS to Clark, Alexander, 1950; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, A-B, Lewis, McMillan, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, C-D, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence, E-G, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, H-K, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, L-O, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence, P-R, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, S-U, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, V-Y, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 11)
        - Unidentified correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - McCombs, William Frank, Shorthand notes in connection with 1911-1912 campaign, 1911-1923; 1 box
        - Shorthand notebooks 1 and 2 of Lyons, Maurice F., McCombs, Maurice F, 1911-1912; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - Shorthand notebooks 3 and 4 of Lyons, Maurice F, 1911-1912; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - Shorthand notebooks 5 and 6 of Lyons, Maurice F, 1911-1923; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 3)
        - Shorthand notebooks 7 and 8 of Lyons, Maurice F, 1911-1912; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - Shorthand notebooks 9 and 10 of Lyons, Maurice F., Lewis, McMillan, 1911-1912; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 5)
        - Transcript of notes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 6)
        - Diaries and notebooks, undated; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - General, 1897-1952; 1 box
      - 1 TL (copy) to Sedgwick, Ellery, Baker, Newton D, 1922; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - 1 TL (copy) to G. P, 1919; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - TLS to Vreeland, W. V., Baker, Ray Stannard, 1925; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - TLS to Ross, Millard F., Beach, Henry C, 1910; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - ALS to "Dear John" Cabot, Richard C, 1910; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - 50th anniversary dinner of class graduation. Presby, Frank, Secretary, undated; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - TLS, to McKean, Dayton D., Close, Gilbert, 1929; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - TLS, to Boyd, Julian P., Cook, Pierre '92, 1942; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - ALS, to "Dear John", Curtis, Charles P, 1922; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - TLS Clemens, Cyril with TMS 1938. Daniels, Josephus, 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - TL (copy) to Fine, May, Fine, Henry A, 1913; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - TLS to Lupfer, Robert M., Galt, George McF, 1916; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - TL to "Margaret", Kloeber, Charles Edward, 1918; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - 2 TLsS, to Mendenhal,H. G. 1919. Lane, Franklin K, 1913; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Photostatic material regarding the League of Nations and including correspondence between Lodge, Henry Cabot and Myers, Denys P., letters to Myers by Macauey, C. R. and Marburg, Theodore, an address by former U.S. Senator Hitchcock, Gilbert M., the "Hitchcock Reservations" by Wilson, Woodrow, etc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence between Moors, Mrs Moors, and Barker, Newton D., Ewing, Edward H., Fuller, H. W., Peabody, George S., Pierce, Myron E., Rutan, Elizabeth Y., Toy, Nancy, Tsurumi, Yusuke, Wilby, Charles B., Moors, John (chairman of the Wilson Foundation), undated; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence replies to invitation to Wilson, Woodrow, inauguration Princeton University Inauguration Committee (class representatives and honored guests), 1902; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence replies from universities. Princeton University Inauguration Committee, 1902; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Lists of invited guests, form letters. Princeton University Inauguration Committee, 1902; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - ALs to "Dear John" Putnam, Elizabeth C, 1922; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - TL (carbon) to Shannon, Peabody, Frederick F.,Undated, 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - TL (copy) to Editor Brooklyn Daly Eagle, 1923; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - TL (copy of extract) to "A. Wilson, Woodrow and friends" Smith, Esther Morton, undated; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - ALS to Ross, Millard and others. Spurgin, William H. '98, 1910; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - TLS to "The Library of Princeton University". Watts, George W, 1952; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - 2 TLsS to Isham, William B. Jr. Wilder, William R, 1897; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence with the Conseil de'Etat de la Republique et Canton de Geneve, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - TL (Photostat) by Swezey, Anthony Clinton to Dodds, Harold W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - Printed letters, "The Woodrow Wilson Democracy, 1921-1922", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - Unidentified Correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Bragdon, Henry W., Collection of Reminiscences (Correspondence and Interviews), undated; 3 boxes
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Microfilm of the Henry Bragdon collection of records of personal interviews and correspondence is available.
    - List of contents of the Bragdon, Henry W., Collections, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Henry Bragdon, compiler. Memorabilia of Woodrow Wilson, a collection of records of personal interviews and correspondence. Microfilm., undated; 1 box (Box 117)
    - Andrews, Evangeline W., Bryn Mawr College, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Andrews, Charles M., Johns Hopkins Univ., Crew, Henry, Dewey, David R., Diamond, William, Doetsch, Louisa, Finley, John H., Freidal, Frank, French, John Calvin, Goldman, Eric F., Hunt, Rockwell D., Powell, Lyman P., Ross, Edward A., Shaw, Albert, Thieses, Frieda C., Wetzel, William A., Williams, Langdon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Agar, Scott, (Mrs.), Princeton University, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Allison, J. M. S., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Ashburn, Frank D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Professor Bainbridge, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Baker, Ray Stannard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Beam, Jacob N., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Brakeley, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Brand, Katharine E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Brigham, Carl C. (Mrs.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Browne, Charles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Burlingame, Frederick (Mrs.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Capps, Edward, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Carpenter, Farrington R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Clark, Alden H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Clemons, Harry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Compton, Karl, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Conklin, Edwin G., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Corwin, Edward Samuel, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Cram, Ralph Adams, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Crew, Henry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. Cuyler, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Davenport, Frederick M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Dabney, Richard Heath, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Daniels, Winthrop M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Dawson, Edgar, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Delpuech, William, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Duffield, Henry G., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Dulard, James P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Furell, Fletcher, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - Durner, William J. (barber), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - Elliot, Edward, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 35a)
    - Fager, Mary Spousler, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - Farrand, Max, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - Farrand, Wilson, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 38)
    - Finney, J. M. T., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 39)
    - Fleming, Matthew C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 40)
    - Flick, Alexander C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 41)
    - "Folklore", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 42)
    - Fornance, John Knox, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 43)
    - Fraser, George C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 44)
    - Frost, Henry W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 45)
    - Garfield, Harry A., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 46)
    - Garrett, Robert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 47)
    - Gillespie, William, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 48)
    - Griffith, Ernest, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 49)
    - Hall, Clifton Rumery, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. Hall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 51)
    - Halsey, R. T. H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 52)